Ikenna Anosike

About Me

Uyo 520003 anosike212@gmail.com 07037001657

Hi, I'm Ikenna and I'm a dedicated Python Developer. I work very hard. I care about writing clean, elegant and efficient code. I'm currently looking for the right opportunity to work in an environment that would help me become a better Python programmer

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Personal Details

Date of Birth: 1997-05-10

Highest Level of Education: Undergraduate

Industry: Software Development

Work Experience

Python Developer

Electrify - Jos

April 2019 to February 2020

- Applied best practices to Django development processes to provide software enhancement without disruption for end users.
- Collaborated with quality assurance team to verify correct implementation of all software development changes.
- Wrote highly maintainable REST APIs for our software system, forming core framework earning consistent praise from other developers.

Python Developer Intern

nHub accelerator - Jos April 2018 to January 2019

- Supported software engineering projects in an agile work environment.
- Created interactive sites ranging from e-commerce sites to hotel booking sites using Python and Django web framework.
- Met with the Intern Supervisor on a weekly basis to provide detailed project report and milestone updates.
- Collaborated effectively with members of the software development team and personnel from other departments.
- Wrote clean, clear and well tested Python code for a firm called Logical Address.

Education

Undergraduate in Electrical/Electronics Engineering

University of Uyo - Uyo February 2016 to July 2021

Skills

- Python
- Django
- MySQL
- REST

Links

https://anosike-ikenna.github.io/portfolio/

https://github.com/anosike-ikenna/

https://linkedin.com/in/ikenna-anosike/